Endicott Johnson Workers and Organizers Oral Histories 5695 OH
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Endicott Johnson Workers and Organizers Oral Histories
1981
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Battista, Sylvan
Springer, Lee
O'Conner, Bernice
O'Conner, Roger T., :Endicott Johnson Corporation
5695 OH
1.56 cubic feet
1.6 linear ft.
Oral histories (document genres).
Audio cassettes containing oral history interviews with Sylvan Battista, Lee Springer, Bernice O'Conner and Roger T. O'Conner.
3338502
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 24, 2012
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 27, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5676: International Fur and Leather Workers Union Records 5685: Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Records 5685 mf: Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Records on Microfilm 5685 P: Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Photographs 5917 P: Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Additional Photographs 5922: Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Additional records 5924: International Fur and Leather Workers Union Additional Records 5855m: Endicott-Johnson Photograph of Workers
Shoe industry -- Labor unions -- New York (State); Battista, Sylvan; Springer, Lee; O'Conner, Bernice; O'Conner, Roger T.; Endicott Johnson Corporation
3338502
- Lee Springer, Pres. Bd. Local 285 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Lee Springer (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Sylvan Battista, Chief Steward, Local 285 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Sylvan Battista, Chief Steward, Local 285; Session 2 (Nov. 12, 1981) (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Sylvan Battista (7/13/1981) (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Sylvan Battista (11/12/1981) (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Sylvan Battista, Chief Steward, Local 285 (7/13/1981) (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Sylvan Battista, Session 2 (11/12/1981) (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Sylvan Battista (7/13/1981) - incomplete copy/original not in good shape (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Sylvan Battista (11/12/1981) - incomplete copy/original not in good shape (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Roger and Bernice O'Connor (4/7/1981) (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Roger T. O'Connor and Bernice O'Connor (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Roger & Bernice O'Connor (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Roger T. O' Connor & Bernice O'Connor (Box 14, Folder 1)